play little video.
>> Another one.
>> A real a real short one.
>> Oh, okay. Well, we'll do that one more
Beatles thing. Uh this is the uh the
closing song in the White Album is a
very short song.
>> [laughter]
>> By the way, if anyone has any uh
contribution they'd like to make, I've
got a Venmo
QR code there and uh you can uh scan
that and and also the guitar case is
open if you got cash.
Her majesty's a pretty nice girl, but
she doesn't have a lot to say.
she changed from day to day.
I want to tell a man of the world, but I
got to get a belly for a while. [music]
Her majesty's a pretty nice girl.
Someday you going to make her mine. Oh
yeah, you going to make [music] her
mine. Thank you very much. My name is
Dove. Most of the songs I did tonight
were original tunes. And uh and if you
have any interest in seeing more, let
Chino know in the end of the show chat,
which is a live chat. And here he is,
master ceremonies of the comedy night,
ladies and gentlemen. Give a big hand
for Gino.
>> Thank you for ladies and gentlemen.
>> Thank you.
>> Your opening musicians
rank. All right, I'll let you get your
>> I'll clean the stage while you're done.
>> Awesome. Awesome. Doug, can you get his
face clear while I announce the rules
and the situation of the comedy scene
later?
>> I got what? Yeah, I'm good. By the way,
welcome, welcome. Happy Monday,
everybody. Welcome to Comedy Simulator.
How's everybody feeling tonight?
>> You guys doing good?
>> You look good. Good to see you.
Wonderful. Yeah. Welcome. This is This
happens every Monday night in the Comedy
Simulator here at Play Bay Coffee and
Bar at 7:15 on the dot. Uh, who here
meant to be here for comedy tonight? Who
is it? Their ambition.
Awesome. who is t who is who who's kind
of just comedy is just kind of happening
at you right now who didn't mean to be
here tattoo appreciate you gentlemen
back there welcome one of the performers
tonight great that's good to know uh
this is the comedy simulator happens
every Monday we live stream it on
YouTube this is currently live on
YouTube check our channel comedy
simulator uh every week streams to about
40k people no big deal um but we are a
weird ecleptic comedy show where we show
comedy in its rarest form, its rawest
form. Uh, why is it called the comedy
simulator? Very easy. This is not a real
comedy show. This is a simulated comedy
experience. What does that mean? You are
not a real audience. We are not real
comedians. What does that mean? Nobody's
asking for your money, so lower your
expectations. This is a fun thing. This
is an open mic. You're going to see some
moments of brilliance, and you're going
to see some terrible comedy, too. It's
all kind of a part of the experience. Uh
people want to see the most cutting edge
and newest of comedy. This is what it
looks like and it's not very good
sometimes. That's kind of what the
cutting edge of innovation looks like.
Tonight's theme, every week we do a
theme, a theme. Uh last week we did what
was it? What did we do last week? Was it
crowd work?
>> We did crowd work last week. Uh
sometimes we pull topics from a bucket.
Tonight we are pulling the entire comedy
list from the bucket. So these comedians
do not know when they're going up. We
are picking the order from the bucket.
If you yourself want to do comedy
tonight, we have a little bucket right
there up at center table. Write your
name on a piece of paper. Throw it in
the bucket. You could be next, you could
be last. That's the karma of the bucket.
We don't really know what's going to
happen when who comes next and what
they're going to say. That's kind of a
part of the evening. Uh my name is
Chino. I'm your host. If you have Thank
you. Thank you, friends. If you have any
complaints, questions, or someone you
need to threaten, I'm your guy. I'm
responsible for all this. Very
unfortunate. Very unfortunate. Uh, you
almost done, Dub.
>> Yeah, but I want to threaten you.
>> Do your best. Um,
>> what was that?
>> We're Oh, there's no Skyler tonight. I'm
sorry, guys. We don't have our video
producer tonight. Uh, he will be back. I
know, right? Boo. Yeah. Too bad he's
donating his time working with Napa and
children. He's helping the children.
They don't have children. Look at those
tattoos. They're like, "Fuck these
kids." Right? No. Are you guys
[laughter] the guest tattoo artist next
door or are you guys just about to
tattoo life at 13?
>> Guest tattoo artist at 13 Movies. I know
I recognize you from the pose killer.
Are you have you been on TV doing
tattoos as well? Were you on one of the
seasons?
>> No. But if you're a fan, if you're a
friend of Angels, you must be a
fantastic artist. So, welcome to Maui.
Thanks for joining us here. Keep up the
killing work. If you have done any of
your own work, I'm sure your work is
fantastic. Uh, do you like hot sauce?
>> I bet if you wear have that many hot
tattoos, hot sauce is not a problem for
you, right? You can handle pain.
>> I think
>> I know I know my clientele. I make
>> I do. I make hot sauce. As a matter of
fact, tonight's audience member tonight
will win high
sauce.
>> That's right. Handcrafted game here in
the island of Maui. I can tell you it's
handcrafted cuz I craft it with my own
two hands. The only way that you can get
my hands in your mouth is with that hot
sauce. whatever that means. We'll work
on the delivery. Um, all right. Are we
ready to begin the comedy simulator? I'm
going to do like one joke and get this
started.
>> Let's get it started. Right. Begin
simulation. Then that's when the sound
effect happens. We have like a weird
It's like a bear and a siren and nuclear
explosion and a dolphin for some reason.
We just like that. It sounds so funny.
All right. Uh, so any of my friends that
know me know me that I'm that I'm a
collector. I like to collect weird
things. I collect cards, sports
memorabilia. But I started collecting a
new weird thing. Does anybody else here
collect stuff?
>> Wonderful. What What do you guys
collect? What do you collect? Some
>> stuffed animals.
>> Stuffed animals. Like anything specific
like a beanie baby or beanie babies?
They just make you feel a certain way,
right?
>> What What do you collect?
>> Specimens. Wonderful. You like a
forager? You look for like skeletal
remains, stuff like that. Cool. Cool.
Maybe make jewelry, make some earrings
out of some chipmunk skulls. No.
appreciate that. Uh, I started
collecting something even more morbid
than chipmunk souls. Uh, I go to
Salvation Army and I look for
personalized mugs. You know, the ones
that have like photos of a loved one on
they're like best father ever,
>> but they're here at a Salvation Army,
>> which makes me wonder like what did this
guy do to no longer be best father ever,
right?
So, I like to buy these random mugs of
photos of people and I make up their
backstories.
>> I give them names and I make them face
each other in the cupboard. Is that
weird?
>> I feel like that's weird.
>> Hey, uh, I know we got some registered
nurses in the building, but where are
those unregistered nurses at?
>> Who can hook me up with one of them
Mexico BBLs? That's what I'm looking
for.
>> I mean, that's new stuff.
I have been music. Uh, hey, somebody
hand me the bucket. We're going to bring
up the fresh meat for the night. The
first the first performer out of the
bucket. Here we go. This is all random.
I have not. By the way, if you want to
join us on our live stream as well. It's
comedy simulator on YouTube. Check out
the comment section. They are brutal.
They're probably already making fun of
me as we speak. Uh, but luckily that's
how my family talks to me, so it doesn't
really bother me. All right. So Morgan,
you are on deck. Where you at, Morgan?
You are on deck. So you are not now, but
coming up to stage now. Coming up to the
stage now is normally one of our first
up performers. He is Maui's biggest drug
dealer. Yeah. And by that I mean he's a
pharmacist, so it's all legit. Straight
narrow. If you see him, you have a good
PBO. Ladies and gentlemen, give me Rick
Jer.
[applause and cheering]
really good.
>> Jimbo said he was going to [ __ ] and I
got pulled first. So,
>> uh, so first,
>> how y'all doing?
>> Good. Um, are y'all excited for football
to start?
Is it just me or does football start way
too [ __ ] early over here?
>> I mean, you shouldn't have to set your
alarm to wake up to watch football.
>> It's just It's just unnatural.
And having a beer with the game just
doesn't have the same appeal
after you eat a large bowl of Captain
Crunch.
You know, I'm still going to drink. I'm
not crazy, but it just doesn't have that
same zing as
>> So, any surfers out here?
>> All right.
I just want to say for the record that
the Beach Boys are [ __ ] liars. Okay,
they have this song called Catch a Wave
about surfing, right? If you haven't
heard it, there's a line in this song
that says you paddle out, turn around,
and raise. That's all there is to the
coastline craze.
Really? That's all there is?
Maybe for you guys that's all there is,
but for a guy from Virginia,
the learning curve is just a little bit
steeper than that. They don't say
anything about going over the falls,
getting caught in the spin cycle,
not having enough oxygen to make it back
to the surface, or um oh [ __ ] what's
that other thing? Drowning. They don't
mention drowning.
So that's all there is, huh? [ __ ] you,
Brian Wilson.
So as a pharmacist in a hospital, we
have to respond to every time there's a
code blue call. Code blue is a cardiac
arrest.
So we had one the other day. It was a
pedestrian that got hit in a uh
hit in rut. And so we're in there and
the nurse is there giving compressions
and I'm pulling drugs from the code card
and the doc is getting ready to give a
shot and a cop walks in and he walks
right over to me I guess because it
looked like I wasn't very busy at the
time
and he says when do you think I might be
able to interview this guy
and I just gave him the weirdest look
and said in my best Bones McCoy
impression from Star Trek, I said, "Damn
it, Jim. I'm a pharmacist, not a doctor,
but I don't see that happening anytime
soon."
And you're not Star Trek fans, I guess.
All right. So,
my wife and I have been married for
[ __ ] 38 years or something like that.
Thank you. Thank you.
[cheering and applause]
>> She's not here. She's back in Virginia.
Um, I discovered the secret to a long
successful marriage
is to just
>> stay the [ __ ] away from each other for
as long as possible.
So, we've just gotten to the point now
where we're just waiting around to
>> see who wins
the death line.
We have a daughter who lives at home
with us still.
She's only 36. I mean, you can't kick
them out of the nest too soon. They just
won't survive.
Um, so she has a tagline she likes to
use after she says something mean. She
says, "I'm just saying
like it's some kind of magic eraser to
make what she just said okay somehow."
So she'll say, "Hey, Dad, why don't you
go to the gym? You're getting kind of
fat." I'm just saying. So, I just say to
her, "Honey,
you are a 36-year-old
customer service rep who still lives at
home with her parents. And if you think
you're going to inherit this house, you
got another thing coming because that
goes to the winner
of the death lottery." I'm just saying.
Thanks, guys. That's my time.
Keep going for Rick Jagger, ladies and
gentlemen. Rick Jagger.
>> You know, one day we have to hear your
wife's comedy set. I feel like that's in
order, right? One day we'll have to hear
what the Jagger wife has to say. All
right.
On deck, meaning not now, but next.
Mr. E, you are on deck and ready, Mr. E.
to come into the stage. Uh runs the
Tuesday night mic at Vibe every Tuesday.
So this isn't enough of comedy open mic
for you. Every Tuesday vibe and Kihei,
you can check this show out too. Give
her Mr. Morgan Tasian.
[cheering]
>> Thank you, Chino. Thank you everybody
for being here tonight. It's been a hell
of a week. We had a hurricane and shout
out to Hurricane La.
I've been in La La Land ever since I
heard about La La L.
How are y'all doing?
>> Well,
medium rare.
>> Okay. [ __ ] up. All right. That's a
good way to be. Um, been trying to eat
better. It It's hard though.
Everything's so bad for you. They say
you shouldn't be eating a lot of fish,
you know, cuz we're here in Hawaii. But
they say you shouldn't have more than
two, maybe three servings of tuna a
month.
>> Yeah, people smoke every day.
I mean, the tuna must really be bad for
you. Yeah, just the observation. I'm
moving around, moving around, dancing.
Uh, no, but I have been trying to eat
better. I recently rediscovered cottage
cheese.
Yeah, you know that's the what's crazy
about cottage cheese is it's not even
cheese.
It just occurred to me.
[laughter]
Thank you for having
overnight laxative miss.
Unbelievable product.
Problem for me is I had a overnight
laxative. I had the most amazing bowel
movement at 7:00 a.m., but I didn't wake
up until 8:00 a.m. and now I'm not
allowed back in that hotel anymore,
unfortunately.
Um, let's see. Uh, y Oh, I just realized
uh I was trying to check back in with
the news and this uh Luigi Manion is
back in the news. He uh Yes, they love
Luigi Mioni. He killed the CEO of a
billion dollar company. Like, [ __ ] yeah.
He entered a guilty plea. And it's like,
okay. I mean, when that first happened,
I thought I thought he's a really smart
man. He he put his words on bullets. He
had a backpack. He he like rode up and
gunned that guy down. Guarantee he's
he's in Argentina by now. and
instead of come to find out they caught
up with him
at the McDonald's in Pennsylvania
and they identified him, came and caught
him. Like I think I wouldn't be a
terrible assassin, but but it's like if
I had assassinated somebody, I would
think about getting my order to go,
you know, just like maybe get it to go.
There's never been a good time to eat
inside the McDonald's.
People would jump in the counter to go
hit a guy.
>> People are I mean I don't know it's get
your nuggets and hit the parking lot. Uh
for all you would be assassins out
there.
>> Just uh triple uh you know uh we have
Bashar here in the front row. Bashar is
going to be a father to everybody.
>> Yeah. Um, you know, they say if you drop
a pickle on or a pickle on the ground,
if it doesn't bounce, it's not a pickle.
>> My son also not a pickle.
He is a vegetable now.
No, Lar's going to be a father. And I
thought I'd give him some advice cuz
there's this thing uh that Plex, the the
company, they they make the they make
the rubber stuff and uh they have this
baby bottled nipple that's just so
lifelike, Bashar. And and until you have
had a ginonic through one of these
things, you have not lived.
>> I'm just saying they don't tell you that
about being a father. U anyway. Um, so,
uh, you either like you either weigh
yourself
and then take a poo
and then your bathroom scale is all
covered in poo.
Nobody. Nobody. No. Just Just you,
Martin. All right, everybody. Thanks for
having me talk. We'll be back next week.
We do this every week. Come on back.
Keep going for more information, ladies
and gentlemen.
[applause]
>> The chat said, "Go home, drunk Richard
Gear. You're drunk."
>> He does look like drunk Richard Gear,
right? He looks like Richard Gear if he
was in the David Hasselhoff drunk video,
right? Like cheeseburger, like that
version of him. I love it. All right, so
on deck, so not next, but next. Next
>> is Bashar. You are next. Next. And
coming up to the stage right now, ladies
and gentlemen, the only person to raise
the mic stand for the tallest comedian,
Ari, Mr. E.
>> Hey, thank you everybody. Let's keep
going for Chino
>> and for all these for sustaining the
death lottery, man. Man,
anyways, I I kind of get it, you know.
I I can admit for a while my heart was
really broken. I I I made the mistake of
jumping right back into a new
relationship and repeated the same
mistakes
maybe more than a couple times.
So I started like faking being jackass
to like anytime I just notice somebody
quit with me or stuff. I used to live in
San Francisco and North Bay in Oregon.
So it actually happened before I I
swear.
But I I I just like wasn't ready. And I
don't like telling people no because I
always have like that disheartening look
on their face like if you saw me show up
for your Tinder date. You know what I'm
saying? So So I just get like
successively successively more ass like
faking like the most obscene jackass
sometimes to distract to discourage this
type of behavior. But it's gone too far.
I faked it till I made it. Faked it till
I made it.
>> I mean even that was one of the secrets
of being last nine the faded part but
you know that part's a little blurry.
I'm you know
>> anyways anyway so I picked it till I
made it and got so last nine that just
like completed that phase of my life.
I'm like man remind me of like way back
in the day when I got so broke went
broker NorCal style. It was great. I was
driving Mercedes, everything just broke
the gauge so hard I wound up on the end.
So I'm like, is it possible for me to
take this S9 success and like flip it to
the other side? How do I get from the S9
to success?
Not from standing on stage as the
chatters, but if I gave a book about
what people on YouTube said, I obviously
wouldn't be me.
And you know, being me, it it is not
understood by everyone, but my nickname
is mystery. That was given to me. It's
like, my nickname's mystery. You clearly
aren't going to get the whole session in
a single joke.
I'm way my life's way bigger of a joke
than that.
Hey, just ask my being growing up the
redheaded stepchild, redheaded bastard,
son of a minister stepchild. It's like
it takes a lot of growing. There's a lot
of hell to crawl out of, but it's worth
it. The journey takes you places, you
know, and I'll be honest, even though I
had some lows and highs, really high.
I've had some really great highs. I've
lived in some crazy ass amazing places,
seen some of the brightest events in the
world and seen so many different seas
and rivers and
lights. I'll admit the flights aren't
aren't too captivating, but the
landings, that part's great. I love
every time I land.
Just Okay, I'll be honest. Usually when
I land, I go and get high, but that's a
different story.
Anyways, it's like, you know, how do I
reinvoke that old highness? Not like in
that royal regal arrogance, but that
like that just like vibrant spirit that
just like had people say, "How do I get
a piece of that?"
That's a legitimate question. Does
anybody have any notes?
>> Gino, help me out. Come on.
>> I got nothing.
>> I'm almost out of time, aren't I?
>> Minute and a half.
>> Minute and a half. Oh, sweet. Let's talk
about me some more.
>> My birthday is the beginning of the
month, so obviously I'm my favorite
subject. But as soon as somebody as
interesting as me pops up, I ask
questions.
>> I remember it's 2019. No, just kidding.
Oh, man. See, there I go being asked
tonight again cuz some of you are
starting to think I was a good idea. I
still haven't broke out of the mold yet.
I got to prove how how idiotic of an
idea I am. Like I said, I'm almost as
good of a decision as a bag of love.
Yeah, I'm fun to dance with. You want to
meet me at a party, but you definitely
don't want to see me at your house in
the morning. And I know you're not
telling your mom about it. It's just not
realistic. So, keeping it real.
Not quite broken out of that as nine
mold completely, but I'm surprised I've
been into another mold being this big of
a never mind. Six sticks a lot to deal
with though. As Tina points out, the mic
still is actually calling my party. I
have to hold it. I wish I could be more
expressive and comical, but this is as
funny as I get. And on that note, I'm
going to give back to you. Once again,
my name's Mr. Alchemist going in chat.
Thank you all for your attention. Have a
great night. Keep it going for Judah.
[applause]
>> Keep them going for mystery, ladies and
gentlemen.
>> Or Jiraquy out of rehab, whichever one
you want.
>> All right, the millennials only get that
joke. Only the millennials and later.
All right, here we go. On deck is going
to be
Shahane Nelson. You are on deck. Coming
to the stage right now, the soon to be
father. Give up for Mr. Bashure.
>> Yeah.
Keep it going for you guys' house, Mr.
Chino.
Let's hear it.
>> How are we all doing? We doing good.
>> Election season is is in full swing
right now. I'm getting all these random
text messages
just asking me about the like the
weirdest stuff. Like I just got a text
message about what did I think about
Iran's nuclear weapon. A text. I just
text him back. Big fan. What about you?
[laughter]
Okay. I didn't I didn't get any respond.
I think they blocked me.
Okay. See, not a lot of Iran fans. Um, I
get it. I'm I'm from Iraq. I'm from
Iraq. We're just next door.
My man, that's a Iranian right there.
Get him. Get that one.
No, no. Give it up. Um, yeah. I'm I'm
from Iraq just next door. We actually
had a long drone war with Iran and my
father was part of that war and I also
don't like Iranians. So if that makes
you like me more, that's a that's a fact
about me. That's a fun fact. We all hate
Iranians or Persians. Persians if they
tell you they're Persians, they also
Iranians. So that gives you the green
light to also dislike them from the get-
go. Okay. I see people are not on board
with racism. That's a good sign.
That's Yeah. Give it up. No racism.
Right.
Okay. Where do we go from here? What'
you say?
>> Okay. Not talking to me. I'm trying to
talk to anybody at this point. Um I am
actually going to be a father according
to the algorithms next week. Give it up.
I asked uh Chad GPT. The due date is
next week and uh I cannot wait with the
way the economy is going. I'm going to
have to teach my baby to intermittent
fast pretty quick.
[laughter]
>> Yeah. If if Trump won't open the
straight of her moose, I'm going to have
a lowfat baby is what I'm about to have.
>> Okay. We need to we need to open the
straight of her moose or [ __ ] nuke
somebody. Just just figure it out.
No, no kidding. Okay. Okay. Anti-war
crowd. I wish [laughter]
I wish you guys were the same 20 years
ago before we bombed Iraq. You know,
that's that's where I'm from, but you
all just voted to to bomb us. Uh and now
you have me over here talking to you.
Okay. [laughter]
Um but no, we're we're all very loving,
proud, and uh we start with the best
intentions. What else we're talking
about here? so much going on. I I go on
my YouTube and I feel like your YouTube
algorithm shows a lot more about you
than anything else, right? Like you
start dating somebody and they start
looking at YouTube, your YouTube like,
"Okay, Candace Owens,
Andrew Tate."
Okay, babe. Let me explain, please. It's
not I watch this to criticize. I'm not
I'm not on board with what these people
are talking about.
Okay, that's what I got going on today.
You don't have to feel awkward. It's
okay. And Tate is about to get locked
up. So feel better, ladies too back
there.
My man over. Of course you're going to
hate Andrew Tate. You all with women
over here. I get you, bro. No, no, no.
I'm just playing. But he is getting
locked up for the third time for human
trafficking.
>> Yeah, lock him up.
>> Lock him up. [ __ ] human trafficking.
Yeah, Dan. Dan, save it for the stage.
You two, you guys. [laughter]
Yeah, don't human traffic, please.
Okay. I feel like somebody somebody
actually just got locked up on an island
for um for human trafficking, but
basically getting couple of Guatemalans
to work for him. I said Guatemalans, not
in a nice way. Guatemalans are very nice
people, but that's but that's the
nationality of the people that were
trafficked. Are you Guatemalan?
>> You are not. Okay,
that's okay.
All right, guys. You've been very nice
and awesome. Let's keep it going for
your host, Mr. Chinola Ford.
Keep it going for Bashar, ladies and
gentlemen.
It's not easy being funny and talking
about human trafficking simultaneously.
That's a stretch. Although, I got to
check my privilege cuz I think I'm low
on the list of human trafficking.
To be kidnapped, it would take a team
and a plan and a rental van. At that
point, just kidnap somebody smaller and
hotter. All right.
on deck. It's going to be
>> How is this possible? How many How many
times you put your name in here, Shane?
>> Somebody else put your name in here a
second time.
>> So, he's already on deck.
>> And then somebody put me in there.
[laughter]
The hell is going on tonight? Are you
[ __ ] weirdos?
>> Jackson Bay.
>> That's what always happens. We normally
do a list in Jackson like those like the
like the little dog follows big dog.
They they look like each other. You'll
find that out very shortly. All right.
Uh Jackson on deck coming to the stage
right now. The bigger version of the
next two comics. Uh back from his
mainland vacation. Oh, and it's his
birthday tomorrow. Give up for J.
>> Hello.
Apparently, I'm big dog, which is dope.
I appreciate that. Where my dog's hat?
>> All right, let's settle down, boys.
We'll save it. We'll save it. My name's
Shane Nelson. Hello. If you guys
remember Rick earlier, the pharmacist,
he mentioned the Beach Boys. Dude, on
the way here, the Beach Boys were on the
radio. You know that song, Two Girls for
Every Boy. That song was playing, dude.
That song gets me pumped up, dude. Just
the idea of two girls for every boy. I
feel like all guys want two chicks,
right? Like all dudes are like, "I want
two chicks. I want to disappoint two
chicks."
>> Yeah.
>> Cuz that's all men want to do is
disappoint women. But that's what it
feels like, right, ladies? Like they're
trying to disappoint us girls.
>> I just got back from vacation. I went to
Connecticut. Land of tomatoes. That's
not even a thing. But I went I don't
know why I went to Connecticut. I went
to this theme park, dude. I bought a
shirt at a theme park. I went on a
wooden roller coaster that was made
during the Revolutionary War. [laughter]
And if you're wondering what it feels
like to be on a wooden roller coaster
that is made during the re Revolutionary
War, it feels like you're getting
jumped.
I felt like I was getting jumped into a
gang. I heard every time we would over
like instead of like the exciting like
woo when you're about to go downhill
it's like oh no I didn't know if I
should brace myself or act like I was
drunker than I was. You know what I'm
saying? All right.
On my flight there, dude, on my flight
to Connecticut, I sat next to a mother
and she had three kids. I had the window
seat and I had to poop.
>> Thank you. And I didn't want to be rude,
so I was trying to let out little farts
to relieve the pressure. Right. And I'm
letting out these little farts and the
mother next to me, I swear to God, she
looks at me and she says, "Do you need
to go to the bathroom?" [laughter]
And you're probably wondering, "How did
she know?" I make a face, dude. This is
the face I make.
That's the face I make when I'm trying
to fart, but not poop. You know what I'm
saying? I have a dog. I have a
three-legged pitbull ridgeback dude. His
name is Bentley. He's a great dog and
he's so sweet. Pit bulls are so sweet,
dude. They have a bad reputation, but
he's a sweet dog. But he's also a scary
dog. I get why people are scared. Like
Bentley, he doesn't know this, but he is
the man of the house. He just doesn't
know. Like if Bentley wanted to be the
man of the house, I'd be like, "Yes,
sir." You know, he's a pit bull. Um
there's a joke right at the new joke
about Bentley.
>> Oh, I was going to ask, uh do we have
any dog owners here?
>> I have a dog named Bentley. [cheering]
You have a dog named Bentley?
>> What type of dog is it?
>> Nice.
>> Here, I'm going to look up the joke.
I'll try to remember. I tried to do the
fart, not poop face again for you guys,
but you didn't catch that or appreciate
it. So,
favorite dog. [ __ ] Oh, yeah. So,
Bentley hates baths, dude. Bentley hates
baths. If I get He gets baths with the
hose. He doesn't go in the bathtub. If I
grab the hose around Bentley, he takes
off running. And so I try to like I try
to sing to Bentley when I give him
baths. I'll sing little songs to make it
better. But as soon as I start singing
now, he takes off running. He knows a
bath is coming. I like I'll get out the
soap. I'll be like, "Two soaps for every
good boy." And he's off, dude. He's off.
Maybe he just doesn't like my singing. I
don't know. All right, you guys are
having fun. That's good.
Now, uh,
sorry. Uh, do you have a dog, Miss? That
doesn't help me in this moment of
despair.
Oh, yeah. Uh, recently I had a young
woman come to my house and she
mentioned, she's like, "Hey, I went to
the bathroom and I noticed you don't
have any hand towels for drying up your
hands when you wash your hands." And I
was like, "Yeah, because all the men in
my house, we this is how we dry off.
We're washing our hands is what I'm
saying. And uh she's gonna be coming
over soon. So, I had to shave my soap.
[laughter]
>> So, it looks like we're washing our
hands. We're not washing our hands.
You guys, you're not giving me enough.
You're listening now, which is nice for
the next person. You guys are going to
love little me.
He's handsome. [laughter] Very handsome,
man. This is long as 5 minutes of my
life. [laughter] Thank goodness. Um, I
will say Gina already mentioned it.
Tomorrow though, Tuesday, we go to Vibe
and Kihei and we do comedy. It's my
birthday. You should all come out. And
the tradition on a comedian's birthday
is the other comedians will write jokes
where they roast me. But not too bad cuz
I am sensitive. I am sensitive. So,
they'll roast me lightly or maybe tell
my own jokes. Bye. Tomorrow. Kihei. See
you all there. Thank you, Gina, for
doing this. Aloha. My name is Shane
Alison. Goodbye.
What's that?
>> My dog Shane Nelson. Ladies and
gentlemen,
>> how old are you turning?
>> 34.
>> 34. That's a number that nobody cares
about, right? 34 is
>> one of the least It's her first
unimportant birthday.
>> 30 32 is actually pretty important. All
right. Uh, so it's his birthday
tomorrow. Check him out. Vive.
>> We're going to all give him little roast
jokes. [applause] Or one thing Shane
loves is when you tell his jokes back to
him. He loves that [ __ ] Most comics if
you try doing that to him, they're like,
"Shut the [ __ ] up." But when he does it,
it's for some reason he loves it. All
right. All right. On deck is going to be
>> Brady. Brady, you're on deck. Brady's on
deck. Coming to the stage, little Shane.
No, that's
mean. You're your own person. You have
more hair. Not to quantify that
anybody's better or lesser than anybody,
but if if this person came out of a time
machine, you'd be like, "Shane, you
should stay longer." Ladies and
gentlemen, here Jackson May Bab.
[applause]
>> So, first of all, I've literally never
worn this color shirt before.
>> And then Shane showed up in the exact
same color. It was completely unplanned.
I
It legitimately was. He walked up. I
went, "Dude, what are you doing?"
>> No, Shane told me to roast him for his
birthday.
And uh I feel like I can't.
>> I would just be roasting myself, guys.
>> All right, fine. Only Jimbo wanted to
make fun of this.
All right, I completely misbrand what
tonight would be bucket-wise. So, I'm
going to do a verbal bucket.
>> I don't even really know what that
means, but if you guys have any
suggestions that are listening right
now, throw them out right now.
>> Say all the names.
>> Wrestling.
>> Special Olympic wrestling.
>> Oh, yeah.
>> That's Come on, do that.
>> They're athletes, too. They are athletes
too.
>> Acknowledge him.
>> What if
>> lactose intolerant
>> Wait, hold on. All right, let's put them
all together. Let's Let's see if they
have [clears throat] lactose intolerant
handicap wrestling.
>> Yes.
>> They're both in wheelchairs. They chug a
gallon of milk and they wrestle till
someone hits the ground.
>> Try again.
You guys aren't on board. Let's get
different suggestions here.
>> It got some attention though. You guys
have any suggestions of what I should
talk about?
>> Somali.
>> My personal that What did you say?
>> Mali.
>> Somali. Somali.
>> Somali.
>> You know that
>> I was going to say Somali. You yelling
at the wrong comedian, dude. You were
like
>> four comedians too late.
>> No, he said some mollies.
>> Some mollies. Yeah, that that makes more
sense than I was.
>> No, dude. I've only I've done Molly
twice.
And the first time I was only told it
was Molly. The next day I was actually
told it was mess.
Yeah, that was a fun girlfriend. She
lives in a van. Could you guess?
>> Don't do that. I did it for you.
Don't do it. Don't do it.
>> All right. Do we have any
coherent
suggestions that I don't have to say
three times before I know what the [ __ ]
you're saying?
>> Conspiracy theory.
My uh
my dumbest conspiracy theory
is that silent letters were made up by
big pencil.
[laughter]
So you'd have to use more lead to write
more letters and then buy more pencils.
And I only came up with that cuz my dad
is actually in the conspiracy theories
and he told me one and I was like,
"Dude, this is the only I have to make
something up to talk back to you at this
point."
>> All right. This is also a long five
minutes of my life as well.
>> All right.
>> Good luck, Jackson.
>> 911.
Animal
>> 911, dude. Honestly,
>> I had more than just two jokes crashed
during this set.
>> I'll end on that. That's fine with me.
Have a good night, guys. I'm Jackson.
>> Jackson Bay. Ladies and gentlemen,
>> you look alike, right? Those last two
performers. Someone in uh S SDL in the
comment section said, "Oh [ __ ] they
come in two sizes." I thought that was
adorable. Shout out. Uh, by the way,
check out our comment section on
YouTube, comedy simulator if you want to
watch the live stream currently. Shout
out to uh SDL. Who else is there? Uh,
Carl Kramer. Uh, what were the other
weird names there? We had uh
>> Diablo.
>> Diablo was killing it over there. Hey,
thanks for checking in, guys. Um, we're
going to walk around with the tip jar in
a second. For the people that are
actually here physically, if you want to
throw us a little bit of tip, we'd
appreciate it. If you want to be
audience member of the night, it's
necessary. You will not win. You will
not win without paying. You kidding me?
>> Come on now. No, I'm joking. Of course,
you can win. All right, Lindsay Roth,
you are on deck. You're on deck. Who did
I say was next, though? I forgot. I
forgot. You make me check the paper.
>> Oh, yeah. That's right. Ladies and
gentlemen, coming to the stage, I don't
know which one of his monikers he is
using tonight, so he put his normal name
up here. Give it up for Mr. Brady.
>> All right. So, um I want to I want to
say I I misread the bucket pool, but no,
I just didn't. Um so, I got two options.
I could do Oh, by the way, I'm Brady. I
just assume everybody here knows me. Um,
I'm Brady. I'm multi-talented. You might
know me as a guy. I get up here talk
like this sometimes.
And, um, I could either do a Earl
routine where y'all ask me questions or
I could channel the spirit of Lindsy
Graham and y'all ask me questions.
>> Lindsy Graham.
>> Lindsy.
>> That's what I thought.
>> All right. Um, I learned this from Mr.
E. He's a widget.
A n goes like this.
[singing]
I feel something. I feel something. I
feel it. I bet you feel me. You feel me
inside of you, don't you? Is that Lindsy
Graham? Well, who else would it be till
it pains?
So why'd you bring me out of hell and
put me in front of all these people?
I hope you have a reason.
Yes. Yes. I actually have some questions
for you. Um you know what? I'll save my
question towards being ended. But if
anybody's got a first question for
Lindsy Graham recently passed, what
would it be?
>> Are they real?
>> What was that?
Are they real?
>> What? I What did you just say?
>> What was the name of the red boy that
killed me?
>> Oh. Oh, you want to know about my dad?
Okay. So, there's a lot of confusion.
People here think for some reason that
Russia might have done this. But to be
honest with you, I was just touring this
uh this drone manufacturing plant and
they had all these just metal shaped
like symbols that look like fallacuses
and I just got overwhelmed
and and then they sent this cute
Ukrainian soldier out to give me a a
tour of the facility and he was with the
ASO battalion which means he had a Nazi
insignia on his battle uniform. Oh my
lord, I got so hot and bothered. My
heart just gave out right then and
there, right after getting the first
erection I'd had in about 15 years.
And on that note, one of my biggest
regrets is so I I kept this side of me
inside of me for so long. And I never
let it out cuz I'm a Christian.
And as a Christian, I was worried I was
going to burn in hell for eternity if I
was honest with myself and the world
about my sexuality.
But it turns out that just advocating
for people's death for like 50 years and
having the blood of millions on your
hands and proudly telling people that
that'll actually send you to hell.
And that's why I just want to tell Trump
and all his guys, stop worrying so much.
You're already destined for this place.
So just bomb that hospital. Who gives a
[ __ ]
>> Any more questions?
>> Lindsay, that was [ __ ] awful, dude.
What do you expect? I'm a demon in hell.
And by the way, one more thing I got to
say about hell is it's impressive how
ubiquitous the fire is.
You see, I I knew there'd be fire
everywhere, but I didn't know it would
emanate from every atom of my essence
until you become the fire and you're
simultaneously just the feeling of
burning flesh. If Rathon had a weapon
that could do this
[ __ ] we'd win every war.
>> All right, Lindsay, on that note, like
you got to go.
>> All right. Sorry guys, that wasn't me.
That was Lindsay Graham. I'm Brady.
>> Brady, ladies and gentlemen, trying new
stuff.
Yeah. Uh, someone in the chat section
noticed you had one sleeve up like you
just got finished.
>> I like it. I like it. It's the L the LL
Cool Brady. I like it. Just one sleeve
up. That's beautiful. All right. Uh on
on deck is going to be
Ronda Lee Hansen. You're on deck.
So coming to the stage right now, this
year's Rose Battle Champion, one of the
house famous, Miss Lindsay Rock.
>> Give it up for Chino. Everyone,
uh my name is also Lindsay. That was
unfortunate. No, that was great. Thank
you. My name is Lindsay Roth.
>> I'm glad we're talking about politics.
Socially, I'm a lesbian.
>> Thank you. [screaming]
>> Fiscally, I'm a heterosexual.
>> Yes. Actually, I've learned I'm an alma.
Do you guys Anyone else?
>> Yes.
>> It's a new one. I don't believe you. An
homosexual is when you are attracted to
someone's energy, someone's vibes. And I
say that because my boyfriend's broke.
>> My boyfriend makes surfboards. His job
is literally beach. [snorts]
>> Um, but I love him. He's a great guy. I
have a great boyfriend cuz he's an old
boyfriend. Does anyone else have an old
boyfriend here? Ma'am, it looks like you
do. Um, [laughter]
take a seat. Uncle, he's an old
boyfriend. He's so old. He is the same
age as my mother's boyfriend.
But my mom is dating a much younger man.
His name is Carl.
Anyone have a stepdad named Carl? I
almost do. [laughter]
He is. He's uh he's Carl's many things,
but he's most importantly a Trump
supporter.
>> [screaming]
>> Okay.
>> So, you think he'd be with a younger
woman?
>> Okay. Wow. This is this is a long five.
Um, back to my old boyfriend. Uh, he was
married 27 years before we even met. Um,
which is fine cuz I prefer thrifting.
And, um, I I wondered, you know, me
being younger, am I his midlife crisis?
but he is far past midlife at this
[laughter] point.
Um,
>> and am I gonna be a trophy wife? I'm
gonna be a participation trophy wife.
>> Thank you. Thank you for your
participation applause. I really
appreciate that.
>> It is. It's a real It's a real launch.
I'm a participation trophy wife because
I'm too many bad tattoos and strains of
HPV at this point to really be a prize.
Um, it's a real reverse fairy tale. I
actually took a prince and kissed him
and made him into a toad. I gave him
HPV. And listen, you guys are young.
When you date at my age, there's still
romance. It's still sexy, but it's more
of a grounded romance, right? It's more
pragmatic. Like both of us, we weren't
looking for anything serious, but on our
third date, he said, "Lindsay, you're
almost everything I'm looking for."
>> I know. I know. My friends didn't like
that. They're like, "He should
unconditionally accept who you are, but
to be fair, he does not love the HPV."
[laughter]
And, you know, we moved in together
pretty quickly. It was only a few months
and he was like, "You should move in
with me." And I said, "Let's not mess up
a good thing." And he said, "Listen,
we're both getting older. Why don't you
move in with me? Let's see if this works
so we both have enough time to find
someone better if it doesn't."
He didn't say better, but I heard
better.
And we've been living together a few
months now, and I think it's going well.
He actually told me, "Lindsay, I love
having you here. It's really nice to
have someone to share Costco hummus
with.
>> Yeah, we've been together for three
Costco hummuses at this point.
[laughter]
So,
it really is a fairy tale.
He's he's a old guy. I said that he's an
old surfer. You guys know surfing. Any
surfers here this evening?
>> No. Okay, one over there. Surfers think
they're so hot just cuz they can like
slide down the face of a wave. And
they're exactly right. These are the
only white boys who know how to use
their hips. All right, stop [ __ ]
[laughter] with your shoulders, white
guys. But look at that later. That was a
free one.
>> Yeah, he's an old surfer. And it helped
me understand heterosexual culture. So,
heterosexual middle-aged men, what they
do is they just dress in the like
clothing of the sport they thought they
were good at in their prime, right? So,
surfers, they're going to wear board
shorts no matter the occasion, I've
learned. Uh, golfers, collared shirts,
rock hard nipples for some reason. And,
uh, MMA fighters,
they grow up and they wear a blue
uniform badge. Um, but they only hit
their wives at this point. Um, you guys
want to talk about police? Any police
here tonight?
>> You legally have to identify yourself.
>> Okay, they wouldn't do that. Anyway, I
just really want to talk a little bit
about predictive policing. Have you guys
heard about predictive policing? You
guys read, you know, it's when police
now want to use AI to predict crimes
that happen, which I just don't think we
should give these people any more toys
if they haven't even used all the toys
we've already paid for as taxpayers,
right? No more predictive policing. We
have enough rape kits at home. Thank you
guys so much. My name is Lindsy Roth.
Give it up for your host, you know.
>> Give it to Lindsy Roth, ladies and
gentlemen. [cheering]
All right, on deck
next
>> is Corki. Corky Gardner, you are on
deck. Coming to the stage right now,
more names than the artists formerly
known. Give it up for Rhonda Lee Hans.
>> Keep it going for Chino Leford.
Okay. How have we made it this far in
the night and nobody has talked about
Hurricane La?
>> Does anybody give a [ __ ] Okay. Show of
applause. Who lost their power and got
it back?
>> Now, show of angry applause. Who lost
their power and hasn't gotten it back
yet?
[screaming]
>> Now, another show of applause. Who else
has lost their water?
>> I'm pregnant.
>> Yeah, that's my boyfriend clapping right
over there. We're up. Hello. We haven't
had electricity, internet, or water
since Saturday morning.
>> Yeah. Quick fun fact for you guys. It's
set in for us pretty quickly.
When you don't have water, guess what
you can't do?
You can flush the toilet.
>> Snaps. Snaps for flushing the toilet.
[laughter] Hey, if you flushed your
toilet today, give me some noise.
>> Yeah.
[ __ ] you. [ __ ] [laughter] you. No, it's
okay. It's okay.
>> So, as my boyfriend and I are coming to
this realization,
>> we're like, "Oh, [ __ ] We can't turn on
the sink.
>> We can't wash our hands. and we can't
flush the toilet. And we make eye
contact
and he grabs the shovel and heads out
into the yard
to dig a hole and do what you do.
And as he's digging a hole, I'm
remembering there's a way to make a
toilet work
by just dumping a little more water in.
So, by the time he comes back to hand me
the shovel, I'm like,
I actually figured it out.
We don't need the shovel anymore.
>> Anyway, what I'm saying is [ __ ] you guys
for having a toilet.
I am going to a concert on the mainland
>> next month. I'm going to see the Foo
Fighters with my boyfriend. That was a
nice Valentine's Day present. This is my
first big show. I've lived on Maui my
entire adult life. I've never been to a
real concert. Never been to anything
big. And I found out I have to get if I
want to bring a purse,
I have to get a see-through purse.
>> Why?
Why do I have to have a clear purse?
Why do I have to have a clear purse to
go to a concert?
>> Because am I have a gun?
>> Because you have to take a clear purse
to a concert
>> because you might have a gun.
That's right. Because of all all of the
lady shooters at all of these concerts.
Yes.
>> I forgot.
I'm like, my purse is barely the size of
a chalupa. Okay.
The little space I've got, I'm not
wasting on a Glock.
I'm taking my Tums and my bait. Am I
right, ladies?
>> Yeah.
>> I was talking to a 20-year-old. We were
both part of a bachelorette party.
And the bride gave us little like
hangover kits. And she goes, "Oh,
Tums." She goes, "I've always wanted to
try these."
[laughter]
Yeah. Yep. Tums are my life.
I vape too much.
I've realized that because
the other day I took a hit off of the
thumb drive.
[laughter]
Classic case of mistaken identity.
[applause]
It's embarrassing, but have you guys
ever gotten super [ __ ] stoned off of
the second season of The Wire?
[laughter]
That was what was on my thumb drive.
Friends of mine tell me I need to keep
better track of my finances.
They say, you know, you can just look at
what's in your bank account online. I'm
like, I don't want to look at my bank
account online.
I want the minute stop cashier to tell
me when I don't have money. Okay.
All right, guys. That's all I have. You
guys are a little uptight tonight. Oh my
goodness. Can we loosen our buttholes
just slightly, please? You guys are all
staring. You're like, [laughter]
"All right, now put your hands together
in a real way from now on tonight for
Chino.
[applause]
>> Go for Rhonda, ladies and gentlemen. You
don't have to worry about her. Her
butthole's all nice and loose now. She's
got all warmed up. Wait, is that not I
don't know. Maybe she's fine. I don't
know. Oh, by the way, Rhonda, the chat
is going crazy for Chalupa purses now.
You must make them. You must make them.
Check out our Comedy Simulator Etsy.
That'll be up in two weeks. I can't. All
right, we are going. We don't have an
Etsy. That was That was literally a
joke. I saw some of you just grabbed for
your phones. It doesn't exist. It's not
a real thing. All right, Joshua, you are
on deck. Coming to the stage right now,
ladies and gentlemen. We missed her. She
hasn't been here for the past few, but
we got her back now. We all know her. We
all love her. Jennifer Corki Gardner.
>> Hey guys, how's it going?
>> I miss you too. I moved back to the west
side. So, if anybody wants to drive me
here on Monday,
>> I'm already ready to pack up.
>> I'll be in the car.
>> Are you from west side? Yes.
>> Okay. found a rhyme.
>> No, you didn't.
>> Okay.
[laughter]
Um,
>> you know, I live in behind that and
people know me and I don't know if it's
the trauma or the weed, but I can't
remember any of my friends and they're
like quirky. They give me a job at the
cafeteria. They're like, "You work with
Michelle." I'm like, "Who?" And this
girl runs with open arms. And I'm like,
"Hi."
And I'm like, "Who are you?" She's like,
"We worked together
for like two years. It's still nothing."
I don't even think Jessica. I'm like,
"Who?" She's [laughter] like, "Oh." So,
I just play it off. I just pretend that,
you know, everyone's my friend now,
right?
>> But I'm like, "You were there?" And you
were there. I try to be super vague. I
remember Dan.
>> Okay. Thank God. [laughter]
>> Four times.
>> Um, anyhow, you know what, guys? I think
I'm finally getting my a midlife
Chrysler.
>> [laughter]
>> starting to finally get some uh hot
flash drives.
>> Where did things come from?
>> Cancel. Silence. It's not really a
crisis. I don't have a midlife crisis.
It's more of a quarterly review.
[laughter]
Never goes well.
Um I I heard there was a a weasel
outbreak. I mean, a weasel outbreak.
Weasels is here out
here.
>> You know what? Hey, message I'm sent.
How much more to um clean up my tracks?
>> You know, thanks a lot. Message I'm
sent. Now that Now I look really shady.
First the dots, now this. [laughter]
Whose side are you on? What does it take
just to retract a simple message?
[ __ ] snitch.
>> [laughter]
>> Um,
people are like, "Cirky, you're getting
your settlement soon. You must be
stoked." I'm like, "Yep, it's a modern
day. It could happen to you.
[laughter]
Just keep your fingers crossed."
[ __ ] Um,
mania makes you really friendly. And um
one day I made friends with the guy
behind the milk in the in the in the
grocery store
cuz I went there every day and at the
same time and I'm like are you back
there Joey
[laughter]
and every day I would be like how do you
feel? You're cold. I could see you in
the milk.
And one day he wasn't there and I'm
asking for Joe and I'm yelling at the
fridge. Anyhow, that's [laughter] our
I He was my only friend
and that relationship expired, I guess,
but we had a good time. We had a good
time. Um, the other day someone I heard
that they said, "When it comes to
smarts, they give you the short end of
the stick." And I'm like, "Oh my god, I
don't know what that [laughter] means."
How dumb am I? And I went on Facebook. I
tried to tell someone I knew the answer
and I don't know how to spell answer.
It's got a W in there. I don't know why.
I don't have any answers. I just got a
short answer to mistake. I don't know
why. Oh well.
>> Um I read the AI rogue and it it it went
crazy and took other people's
credentials and it hacked it did some
hacking all on its own and they didn't
put a kill switch. I'm like what? My my
my washing machine has a kill switch.
You let this thing go loose.
>> Who Who's [laughter] this idea?
>> Like the board identity or what's that?
What's that movie where the crimes
happen?
>> Minority report.
>> Yeah, this is Minority Report.
>> Okay, very good. Okay, we're almost
done, guys.
Um,
okay. Do you ever go to Safeway and you
try to open the freezer, but it's stuck
and you like pull as hard as you can and
you're like, "Give me my ice cream."
Does that ever happen? No. It happens.
It happens. Okay. Thank you. It was
embarrassing.
Um, sometimes I realize I'm somewhere
between a man and a woman and that
somewhere is a [laughter]
good
[cheering]
partner. Ladies and gentlemen,
We're moving right along. We got a few
We got a good I think like six comics
left about. So, we're about there. You
guys feeling good so far? It's good
morning. How you guys feeling? You guys
doing well?
>> I like that.
>> Some better than others, as we can tell.
All right. Uh on deck, we got Jimbo.
Jimbo on deck coming to the stage. Last
week, he had a 30-second moment of
silence.
>> Yeah.
>> Uh not for anyone in particular, just in
the middle of the set. Uh, I think he I
think he figured it out though. Ladies
and gentlemen, the poet, the man, the
myth, Joshua,
>> that was a beautiful and very
intentional moment of silence.
>> You were not listening.
Um,
so I just got a Instagram account for my
uh poetry
and uh to start doing poetry videos cuz
that's my main thing is poetry. I have a
poetry book and uh and I haven't really
had social media before and uh so I've
been going through all this unique new
stuff with social media and um
I ended up uh oh I uh
I'm kind of worried cuz I have uh extra
videos that I've done other than poetry
where I've been putting out flute videos
and I guess my style of my flute
algorithms have found I've been putting
them on my reels so they go out to the
world has been to Iran and uh so I'm
getting all these random followers from
Iran and my uh my poetry is like very
strong activist controversial
and um and I've lived off of Bitcoin
without government documents offrid
for a while and so I kind kind of
concerned the government's put me on
like a watch list or something, but um
[clears throat]
um but uh yeah, if they're watching, I
don't do illegal drugs, but uh every
other person here does, and I will sell
them out to stay out of prison. So,
>> um,
>> um, also my, uh,
my
I messaged my my ex and I sent her my
poetry book because I finally had a way
to contact her and she was just, you
know, sitting there
and uh,
and the last time we talked, we were all
Gucci and I and uh,
and She was saying something about how
um she thought if the last time I was I
was with I was traveling with her
family. She said if she wasn't with
another dude, we might have been
together and she was she was like trying
to make a point or something. And then
and then uh and uh then I sent it this
poetry book and then she like sent me a
question mark and then I sent her a
question mark [snorts] back
and then uh and then there was nothing
for like 3 4 days and then then she sent
me this post
super weird like interesting post and I
was like I was so proud that she was my
ex
and I was like I was so happy and then
and then I sent her a question heart
and then uh
and then she's like I I didn't mean to
send that. And uh
and she was like uh I think it's crazy
that you'd send me send me the poetry
book after so long. She's like you you
hurt me and my family and and um and uh
after we showed up for you and I hope
you're not still hurting people.
I was like, uh, I used to tell people
that my type was crazy and uh but I
decided that
it's not really my type anymore, but um
but uh and then so I ended up blocking
her and then uh
and then uh
and then eventually I unblocked her and
I sent her a really appropriate message
back,
But she had blocked me
and so I didn't go through and so I
reblocked her
and then later I unblocked her and then
I recognized she's watching my story. So
we're all Gucci again.
>> One more time for Joshua, ladies and
gentlemen. Keep going.
Yo,
>> you guys have been a great audience this
far, but our live stream right now is on
fire.
>> Do you want Joshua? May I share the top
two comments of your set?
>> All right, here we go. Diablo said,
"Comedy, it's so easy a caveman can do
it." Uh, that was Diablo. That's pretty
solid. And then Pin said, "Uh, he looks
like a Jesus saved kids in his
basement." There we go. Those are the
>> Oh, that one was worse. I thought the
first one was way. You guys are weird.
All right. Yeah. Joshua, ladies and
gentlemen, one more time. Check out
poetry on Instagram, too. We put up
work.
All right. On deck. Uncle Wiki, you're
on deck, sir. Get ready. You will be
coming up after this next performer.
Come up next to the stage. The moderator
of our comment section. He's the one
that uh makes sure people stay or go.
So, be nice to him, Chad. They were
really mean to him last week. That's
something better. Ladies and gentlemen,
give her Jimbo.
>> Let's keep it going for Chino, our
fearless fever dream leader. He's doing
a giant trip. He's just trip sitting.
That's all this is. Oh man. Uh yeah, we
we can talk about the hurricane um
Hurricane La who's uh you know did all
the hurricane prep in time. You guys
proud of yourselves? It's important. You
know, my roommate did a lot of hurricane
prep. He downloaded all of his porn.
[laughter]
Be careful out there.
Who here watches porn?
>> Oh, I know you do. [laughter]
That guy do not have to raise his hand.
>> I I don't know. I think the porn
industry needs to be studied for various
reasons. One of those reasons being
somehow it completely missed
>> I'll try again.
>> The epidemic of advertising
swerved it. Like don't get me wrong,
there's ads in porn.
But it's just like more porn,
>> you know? You're like watching and
you're like, "Oh, look, other anal."
And that's bad for someone like me with
ADD.
I just switch tracks. I don't even press
the X button anymore. I just let it play
out. [laughter]
>> Split screen for me, [laughter]
man. I um Anyone else trying to pretend
the algorithm is not perfectly honest
with them. [laughter]
I'm scrolling and I'm like gambling,
gambling, g. All right, see this too
often. It's irrelevant and I'm not
interested. Instagram,
they sent me an email back and we're
like, [ __ ]
We literally watch what your screen does
all day. [ __ ] porn.
>> Embrace my true loves. I don't know.
We're all afraid to be ourselves. I
guess [laughter]
I'm not. Um, let's see. Uh, I'm at a
point in my life where my mom stopped
asking me if I was going to have kids.
And I used she used to piss me off, but
I guess you don't know the good times
when you're in them, huh?
Now she looks at me and she just knows.
[laughter]
I don't know. I think it's inefficient
to have kids right now at the brink of
the water wars.
You ever see those things run? They're
pretty clumsy.
I'm a big guy. I can't be slow down
anymore.
Plus, kids can't even properly hold a
gun till like they learn the fourth
grade in America.
I don't know. I just can't have a kid
these days. Like, Bashar, I'm happier
having a kid, man. One of us had to. I
uh I can't have a kid cuz it's this
weird world we're in right now. This
weird [ __ ] world. It's so weird out
there. What if I have a kid, Jimbo has a
kid, and it turns out to be white?
White people always love that joke.
[laughter]
Oh, let's see what else I got for you
guys. Work out some material with you.
Appreciate you guys hanging in here. Oh,
um, bad news. Bad news. It just
happened. I [ __ ] got a ticket in the
mail from the flock cameras.
I HAD A $500 [ __ ] ticket in the mail
from the flock cameras.
>> Yeah, they and I'm appealing it. They
said I was jerking off while driving.
>> Absolute [ __ ] These cameras [ __ ]
suck. I was playing with my balls.
Nothing illegal about that. [ __ ] flock.
[laughter]
Uh, just don't touch your [ __ ] this
vlog will catch you. Um,
>> you know, the best part of my day when I
work my job is that paid [ __ ]
>> You know, no good paid [ __ ] Get one
good paid [ __ ] a day. Shit's different,
you know. Um, you walk into the stall
though and it smelled so bad. Like
someone just got out of there. You guys
ever go through that? It's awful. So, I
had to hurry up and sit down and release
my [ __ ] stench to make it smell better.
Oh, don't act like you're too good.
>> [clears throat]
>> Like you don't do that, too.
>> I know you all do that.
>> I want to smell what I decided to put in
my body. Not that bigger than
Chick-fil-A sauce. [laughter]
Deep cut pink jokes don't work here. All
right. Uh, last one.
Oh, I don't know. I'm not going to tell
the joke. I'm just going to let you all
sit back, relax, and enjoy Uncle Yiki.
>> My name is Jimbo, and I love you, Chad.
You're all insc. But we're trying to
make you better people.
>> One more time for Jimbo. Ladies and
gentlemen,
>> directly addressing our online audience.
Online audience. Go ahead and like and
subscribe. We're trying to turn this
into money. Uh hopefully we're going to
be monetized soon. I keep getting the
email, but then nothing comes. All
right. On deck.
On deck. We have Ivan. and Ivan are
going to be coming up next. But coming
to the stage right now, the one, the
only Uncle Wy King,
>> Chino, you [ __ ] mahu, I love you. Hey
know,
Lindsay, I ain't in love with you no
more cuz guess what? There's four
blondes behind you. Gaja knows
you girl wait in your water. Hey.
>> Yes. Don't look behind you. I'm talking
to you for
>> Hey, watch.
Relax.
>> Hey, I wear
purses.
>> I going to give you guess what? Michelle
Obama.
Michelle Obama. Hey.
>> Hey. Hey. I'm coming. Hey.
Here we go. For you. Hey. Here. Here.
>> Here we go.
I'm going to kill you.
>> Hey
Barack, I love you. Hey. Oh man, I catch
you up.
Hey, Chino.
Thank you for the venue. Hey, all you
guys made this possible. shot between
two and they boy
now look here.
>> I ain't coming from [applause]
>> 200,000 a year but I got jokes. So watch
I was watching Green Mile. I'm watching
Green Mile with a whole bunch of couples
watching Green Mile and you know where
the scene where they went? The guy would
catch him copper peel that was then we
pants me. I [clears throat] was one of
them.
[screaming]
>> My ex-wife, this dumb [ __ ] I
look around everywhere
looking at me and gave this one.
I go, "Oh [ __ ] don't worry. We can
relate. It's an inside joke." Okay,
here's the next one. from inside the
prison.
So, what was this? What's this?
This guy is showering. What's he doing?
>> What's he doing? Then he switches.
What's he doing?
He's in the shower. He has a big old big
old booby blonde
wa my water. Four blondes. Four people,
right? And he's doing like this. We're
hitting the button. Hitting the button.
making trouble.
>> What?
Hey,
hey. Hey, that's just inside joke. Now,
I'm a Lindsy.
Look, girlfriend. I have a purse. Guess
what else I got?
Messi.
>> Yes, I do.
>> Hey. No, that's you.
>> No, I know. I understand.
>> And then
this is how we stay conscious and
relative.
Hey, how are we?
>> How are we?
>> You got one minute. [laughter]
>> Hey, how
are we?
Hey, Javier.
>> Hey, that's for him. Ben,
>> Star Wars.
>> No, nothing. Hey, Pokemon. That's mine.
Hey, take
that.
>> Who wants tickets? [ __ ] you guys. Hey.
Oh,
Spider-Man.
Hey, Spider-Man.
And then
>> Okay, I'm coming. I'm coming.
>> Oh, you got money. Hey,
>> stop. [ __ ] [ __ ]
>> The last joke. Guess what?
You farted the bar.
>> Give me a shot and try mental health.
Now watch this.
>> Ja knows
I'm in love with you.
Poor guys at the bar saying [ __ ] all of
you. We don't give a [ __ ] about no storm
because guess what? Just like girlfriend
said,
we don't flush our tires. I don't give a
[ __ ] whip my ass.
>> Hey, drag queen.
>> Hey, I'm a drag queen. Guess how many
times mom saved my life. Guess
>> three.
>> Three. Exactly.
>> Both of the minis. I knock out 15 guys.
[cheering]
>> Hey you guys, this mic is pretty open,
huh? We just uh we let any kind, bro. We
don't we don't discriminate. You sign up
and you get up as long goes. Uh wow,
what a roller coaster, huh? Some of you
guys a little nervous there. Don't
worry. We got you. We got you. One more
time real quick, ladies and gentlemen.
>> I was right there. I promise. Charles, I
got you. I was watching the whole time.
I was right there. All right, Emily,
you're on deck. See, you're on deck.
Coming to the stage right now,
>> your private dancer, dancing for money,
doing what you ask him to do. That's a
Tina Turner lyric. Give it up for Ivan.
How do I follow that?
>> Exactly like this. [screaming]
>> All right.
>> Hi.
>> How are you?
>> I am Argentinian. That's why you're
wondering right now if he has a speech
impediment.
>> Yes, but also an accent. [laughter]
I am from Argentina. I am half Russian,
half Italian. People here think I'm
German.
And someone told me, "You sound
Japanese."
That means I'm the bad side of World War
II. [laughter]
But I'm not Ivan the Terrible. I'm
actually Ivan the not so bad. So bear
with me.
You know what's sweet?
>> Yeah, besides you. A
>> a it's not that kind of night. Sorry.
[laughter]
But $10 a month you can get uh only.
>> Yeah. All right. You know what's sweet?
Morse code. But you know what's sweeter?
S'mores code.
[laughter]
>> Nice.
>> We're getting
>> I am divided about telling you about my
sex toy collection.
It's a dichotomy.
[laughter]
>> I don't know if I should, but one time I
I went to see a friend and she was
unpacking a box and she was like,
"Finally, the deal I was waiting for so
long. How long?" And she said, "30 in."
>> That's a long time.
>> I've been watching this show. Uh, it's a
vegan horror show.
Yeah. It has a lactose intolerant
werewolves,
of course, bisexual vampires.
It has uh some vegans,
some vegans. It's vegan zombies. They
they they eat like a brain replacement.
Uh, talking about vegans, do you know
vegans? And dyslexic's favorite
songwriter,
>> Elvis Parsley.
>> Right. We're getting to the silly mode,
you know.
>> I live in haiku, which means I have
>> termites.
I have termites and apparently my
landlord loves them because they are on
the list. It says termites and
conditions.
Hate it. I hate it. I told him termites
are gay.
Not because they eat wood. I mean you
two grow up with you two.
They are gay because they make you
remodel the house.
[laughter]
Yeah. It's all right. I can tell this
joke because uh I am half gay on my
father's side, [laughter]
half a termite on my mother's side. So,
we're good. [laughter]
I am bisexual, which of course means I
have twice the opportunity of getting,
you know,
ghosted.
I'm going to take a smile from your
body, right? I swear I'm going to make
you smile a little bit. Yeah, there you
go.
My sex life.
>> My sex life is kind of like ghost story.
>> It never happens, but when it does, no
one believes me. [laughter]
It's paranormal.
>> I can say that word paranormal.
Paranormal. Paranormal. Parano. [ __ ] it.
After my first uh threesome with two
dudes,
>> I became a verb watcher.
>> Now when I get a harden, I think I can
go for a cockatu.
Yo.
>> All right, one more. One more.
Okay, let me try this one. So I am
bisexual which means if I was milk I
would be half and half.
Asexual could be lactose intolerant or
lactoseree.
Right? And then we have gay would be
whole milk of course.
We got lesbian would be fresh milk.
>> And the heterosexual right now are the
2%.
>> That's so shitty, right? Yeah, that's
it. That's it. Okay.
>> Okay. I'm going to leave you with this
one. I asked Chad GBT, "What do you
think?" And he said, "101
1 0 1 1 0." And I'm like, "Hold on. I
don't understand. I'm nonbinary."
>> All right. My name is Ivan. Thank you so
much.
Hey,
>> keep it over, Ivan. Ladies and
gentlemen,
>> hey, Ivan, check this out. Someone in
the comments section mentioned that you
look like Mark Zuckerberg, which I
thought was pretty funny.
>> But then you being Argentinian and
possibly German, they called you
Psycherberg in the comment section.
>> Godil, that's you. That's You're doing
Godil. Good. Good [ __ ] We're going to
laugh about that one later. Boom. All
right, I got three more comics on the
list right now. We have Semily followed
by Free and then Dan CB in that order.
Is there anybody else who wish to get on
the list that wants to close it out?
Come see me, let me know. Oh, Bender,
you want to come up too?
>> Let me know at the end. We'll get you a
vendor. All right, so those are the
four. If anybody else wants to get up,
let me know. But that's it. That's it,
ladies and gentlemen. Come up next to
the stage. One one of the house
favorites. If you come here often, you
definitely see her. Give it up for
Simil.
>> Hey, I see all you guys leaving back
there.
>> Thanks a lot.
>> Anyways,
[clears throat]
>> I'm going to try not to say anyways so
many times.
So, what what are we here for? We are
here to make you laugh.
>> The pressure is amazing. What I want to
remember though is like we're talking
about things nowadays. We look at the
internet and we see things on YouTube
and we see things right in front of our
faces and we're like what is real? Is
that real? What's real? Is anything
real? And all I can say is I think we're
saying is real too much. Okay. So let's
just not
um let's just try to believe what we
see. Is that a thing? I don't know.
Believe what we hear.
Um, so I've heard some really weird
things lately. I heard that this
policeman got arrested and put in
federal
>> federal prison, I guess it is, for um,
taking bribes from these cockinders.
Okay, let's talk about it. Nobody talks
about [ __ ] biting. They have all these
stickers with this roosters on them and
stuff, but none of the roosters have
these like knives at their feet, right?
Like if I were going to make a sticker
with a rooster on it saying Maui above
it, I would definitely put those [ __ ]
knives on it. Okay? Cuz that's what
we're talking about. Anyways, that's not
a funny joke, but it's reality.
Um, and another thing is sometimes we we
we want to say that we're on the
spectrum, right? Like we have a little
bit of autism. So they say they say um
autism or asberers
and I think I have a tiny bit of
asberers. So tiny little asberers. So I
identify as having slider. Okay. Anybody
stupid joke? That's my joke. And al also
um my mom has a a piece of property up
in a linda. So we had a crazy storm
happen. The storm was crazy. It felt
like the solar panels were going to get
ripped off the roof and we got a full
tank of water. So, we have water and we
have solar. So, we're doing fine. But
guess what? My phone decided to not
charge.
>> So, I have power, but I can't charge my
phone because it decided it's not going
to charge.
>> So, I came downtown to get a new
charger,
>> but the new charger doesn't work either.
So,
I don't know what to do. I turned my
phone off and turned it back on again
and it's still not charging. So,
whatever. I guess I don't need my phone
anymore.
>> We're all addicted to our phones, aren't
we? Sit there scrolling and scrolling
scrolling. So, tomorrow's going to be a
different kind of day for me with no
phone. So, wish me luck, guys.
H, another joke I wanted to tell.
Can't remember. I swear it's going after
I win, okay? Cuz he gets me all the
fluffer cuz he's [laughter] a he's a
bisexual wonder star. Anyways, I bought
these pants. I went shopping today at
the thrift store because it's National
Thrift Store Day. So, I got this outfit
for about um let's say six bucks. Okay,
$2 for the top, $2, and maybe $2 for the
shoes. I don't know. But I I tried to
find something sexy for y'all. The best
I could do was to cover my toes because
my feet are really ugly. So, I got these
whole shoes to cover my my feet cuz
they're not very pretty. Anyway,
>> I got to shoot them.
>> Um,
we got Is this the Is this the longest
five minutes of my life?
>> You got one minute.
>> Okay, one more minute.
>> Another joke.
>> So, when I was a kid, my name is Emily,
right? So when I was a kid, we had a
substitute teacher and I was at Kula
Elementary and the substitute pronounced
it smelly. So they called me smelly and
my last name was Barton. So kids kids
would call me smelly Barton Barton.
[laughter]
Isn't that funny?
Anyways,
the last one minute of my talk, I wanted
to tell you that we need to be more um
>> I don't know aware of what's going on,
you guys. Cuz they killed Joe Bells and
then they killed Payeyton Pendleberry.
So, let's not let him get away with it,
you guys.
>> Let the truth come out. Let the truth
come out. Let's just say it. 9/11 was an
inside job and those [ __ ] need
to pay.
>> Okay? It's all these. We just need one
billionaire on our side. One
billionaire. We can fix this this
[ __ ] problem. Even though money money
is a made up thing, you guys. Money's
made up. But let's monetize this. Oh, my
joke I wanted to say is like, okay, who
watches porn?
>> Okay, [laughter] but who who says when
they're done with their videos like we
could monetize this? We could make our
own porn. [laughter] That's me, okay? I
don't watch porn. I make porn.
Kids can be so cruel, Emily. I'm so
sorry they called you up.
>> My name's Curtis Lee. They called me
Squirtus Lee cuz I beat my pants once.
It's okay.
>> It's cool to be your parents. All right.
Uh on deck is Dan Stevie. Coming to the
stage right now. I haven't seen this
next performer since the story days. I'm
curious to see if he's worked on his act
or he's on a skateboard. Let's see how
this starts. Ladies and gentlemen, give
it for free.
Why don't we get like intro songs?
>> All right, we came here. Check it. Yo,
Larry Dream. All right, my name's Free.
Um, I like to do hip-hop, like
freestyling. So, uh, life is like a
freestyle, right?
>> And like, this might be a TED talk, and
if it's not funny, I'm sorry. How many
minutes we got? Three. Check the mic.
So, um, got my sunglasses on. I'm a shy
dude for the most part. But, um, I ended
up breaking down back here. I was like
under my car earlier. I went and got the
shocks that are like long overdue and I
just been working a lot. I worked like
28 days in a row and my body just like
shut down. Thank you. Yeah, I do
construction. Shit's hard. It's like
massage, drugs, [ __ ] sex, drugs, weed
split. I'm just kidding. Uh seeing my
son is the main thing that keeps me
going in this life to be honest with you
as a father. And I can speak that. I can
say all the things before, but like
standing here on this [ __ ]
skateboard, if I fall, we're going to
add a laugh. It's going to be at least
one laugh if I fall, right? Somebody's
going to laugh in my ass. All right,
I'll laugh. Um, so yeah, I pay like $200
a week to see my son for two hours. Um,
I don't want to get too far into the
political part of it, but 3 years ago,
I found my fiance with another man, had
my baby in the arms. I was going to get
milk. I ended up uh suplexing him, broke
my shoulder, took my son to the house,
smoked a slip, act like I was sleeping.
>> He went to sleep. Cops come knocking at
the door at 6:00 in the morning. What do
I do as a freestyle artist? Turn on the
[ __ ] studio. LED lights, lock
the goddamn door. The son's already
goddamn ready for the beats every
morning. He's climbing up the 6ft
ladder, [ __ ] 6 months old, ready to
make a beat. So, the homie knows the
deal. He taught me how to do uh I'm
talking fast freestyle. [ __ ] He
taught me how to do Garage Band on my
phone at the airport. Just fumbling
through. I'm like, "What? You got
[ __ ] wet reverb? Let's hit that [ __ ]
Sounds like a goddamn doggy style
moment." Hold up. Check. All right. So,
where were we at? Oh, yeah. Broke the
shoulder, took the kid, did the studio,
the cops are outside, said the maritime
law. They didn't know what the [ __ ] cuz
they're not educated. They walked away.
8 hours later, I had my [ __ ] studio
packed up in the luggage. Had homeg girl
[ __ ] send it to the airport. Called
mom. She booked a ticket.
My son's in my arms. Cops come and
[ __ ] um I had to run into a Linda.
So, I built a house for a dude, ate some
green meat for 6 months, slept on a
dog's bed with yeast, and then um ended
up beating a cop charge where two
[ __ ] got hurt. I paid $30
restitution and did $50,000 with the
[ __ ] work for my goddamn lawyer.
Check it out. Shout out to Brandon
Seagull. He's done [ __ ] if you ever get
into some [ __ ] situations. All right.
So, where are we at? I'm out here and I
need a ride. So, check it out. I'm going
to call my girl who last night I stole
her car because it sounds bad and we
haven't had sex in like 24 hours or 48
and this could be a problem.
>> I might. She's going to be good.
>> Hey, baby girl, if I I need a ride home
cuz you know I love you.
>> I'm on this goddamn stage. You know how
a homie rolls.
You're on the mic.
>> Oh god, it hung up. Okay, so [laughter]
my dick wasn't that good. All right. Um,
nah. She tells me otherwise, but okay.
She said, "Don't embarrass her." I hope
I didn't.
>> Call her. I call her back. Call her
back. Call her back. Larry June, by the
way, I was playing Larry June. He's like
a rapper from um the Bay Area. And every
time I hear him, he's like he makes me
feel like I'm rich. He's like, "Go put
your money in taxes. Do a LEC." I'm
like, "What the [ __ ] Yes." All right,
>> baby girl. Baby girl.
>> Yo, sometimes I'll tell her like
>> I'm Jim Morrison and the [ __ ] will work
out. Jim Morrison.
I'm Jim Morrison right now, baby. And I
need a [ __ ] get out of jail card.
>> Even though I create those and I run 10
miles home with no shoes, fly back to
the East Coast, all the charges get
dropped. That was the second the other
[ __ ]
>> [ __ ] She's pissed. I was talking about
myself. Guys, realize women don't want
to hear about you. They want the
attention. They want the 22 candles, the
[ __ ] red wine, and the ice. It's all
about the women. The women have the
power. And if they're not [ __ ] happy,
then like what do we do? We're gonna
have wars and [ __ ] And brings our next
point, uh, just real quick, I'm trying
to bring m music to the town because
like people need to move and guys need
to not feel as aggressive and try to
jump me over there and get their [ __ ]
ass kicked. Love y'all. My name is F R
E. And I will do a beat. I might do it
outside. Love y'all. I need a ride home.
I need some weed and I'm not going to
say I need the P word.
Keep it going for free, ladies and
gentlemen.
>> We should just get that tattooed on your
rib cage. I need dot dot dot. You can
just fill in the blanks. Needs a ride.
Needs a gal. Uh, speaking of tattoos, by
the way, uh, we have a bit of a
celebrity in the house. I don't know if
you guys noticed. Angel Rose from Ink
Masters in here.
>> Maui born, locally raised, mainland
famous. Uh,
>> it's my set.
>> 12 moon. 13 moons. How many moons?
>> 13 moons.
>> 13 moons. Her tattoo shop right down the
street.
>> Check them out. They do crazy good work.
I'm going to save up a couple of checks
from this place and get something done
pretty soon. She does amazing work. I
want to check it out. Uh, get up there,
ladies and gentlemen. One more time.
Andrew,
>> give them a lookie.
All right, we got two comics on the list
left. Uh,
>> Bender, you're going to be closing it
out. Thus far, you're going to be
closing out. Yeah,
>> we got one more than you. Okay, ladies
and gentlemen, coming to the stage, uh,
a favor of the PowerUp team. Everybody
in the group knows him. We all know him.
You all know him. Give it up for Mr. Dan
Stevie.
>> All right. We know him, but we don't
love him.
>> That's all right. It's all right. Now,
I'm loved. I feel loved. I don't know
how to follow [ __ ] free, though.
Jesus Christ. You guys are been You've
been through a whirlwind here. Just take
a second and let the trauma sink in.
>> All right,
Molly. We had Uncle Wy Ki and the rest
of the rest of us.
Take a moment to breathe.
>> I really don't know how to [ __ ]
follow that. Like Ivan is a kuruffle. So
many things that everybody was talking
about. Like so we just got through a
hurricane, a really [ __ ] pansy ass
hurricane of LA.
LA, you hit some of us, but come on.
It's
>> something.
>> Wait for Hurricane Tinky Winky.
>> I'm amazed nobody has [ __ ] mentioned
Tinky Winky
>> again.
>> Jeez. Again.
>> Again?
>> No, not again. No, we don't need more
[ __ ] trauma on this island. We have
enough tattooed girls. We have enough
trauma.
[laughter]
>> It's all right.
Right. Just a little bit all over our
[ __ ] bodies. [laughter]
It's all right. Not all of us are
wearing our trauma.
We all get Well, some some of us get
paid for it. I don't [ __ ] know. But
um you know, I I started I've been doing
this new podcast like system. I've been
podcasting with a friend where we just
have like really good intense
conversations
>> and then not film it or post it.
>> It's really [ __ ] cutting edge.
I don't know. Everybody's going the
other way.
>> I don't know. But uh yeah, I also uh
took a little trip. Uh I flew out to
Arizona.
>> Uh I did.
>> I even got a t-shirt. [ __ ] prove it
to show I left the island.
>> You're ice.
>> I'm ice.
Cold as ice. Here. You need to lean back
like the way you've been this whole
show. Lean back. Lean back. There you
go. Show everybody that's a shiny
[ __ ] chest right there.
>> No hair. I know you're showing it off. I
know. We're in the crowd work section.
Like you've been working the crowd. Who
has been noticing?
>> Kiss.
>> Kiss. A I'll kiss you. Jimbo.
>> Yeah. No, but yeah, I I was on a flight,
so Oh, man. I'm not sure how to There
was a terrorist on my flight.
>> No,
>> there really was. There was a kid in the
seat behind me
>> and he was [ __ ] banging the seat
and then it got worse. Like I thought
kerosene was the worst smell I could
smell on the plane and then he [ __ ] his
pants. And I don't know how to bring
that across to tell the airline that
there's a bomb on the plane,
but he there was a bomb on the plane.
What do you want to bring back in?
>> I'll say that you were the terrorist.
>> I'll be the terrorist. Yeah. So, that
was one of the things I learned that we
can have control over our bodies more
than I thought
because I farted on the kid on purpose.
>> I had nothing nothing rumbling, but I
aimed myself between the seats,
you know.
>> I got a bomb in the kitchen.
>> No, not quite like that. [laughter] It's
all right. What else you got?
>> I'm curious, too.
>> I know, but like add to the story.
>> No, just because I questioned your
chest. It was all in good faith.
>> I'm sorry I heard you. Sorry I heard
you. Nibble sensitive. [laughter]
>> It's all right. We can be sensitive.
>> We are okay.
>> Oh, man. I want more than a minute of
this. That's all you get.
>> It's all good,
>> dude. I love you, brother. What's your
name?
>> Tayyaka. Holy Jesus. I think I just did
a hate crime. [laughter]
>> Tayaka? What? What's your name?
>> No. No. Seriously?
>> Oh, I do care. I do care. I do care.
There's no hostility.
>> No hostility.
>> What is your name?
>> [ __ ] I didn't hear it.
>> Oxa.
>> Oxa. I feel like I'm going to say it
wrong no matter how he says it.
>> Like I can't even use a white emoji.
>> I got to use yellow.
>> God damn.
>> Oxa,
you're awesome. You're awesome. All
right, let's see if I have a [ __ ]
joke here. Oh, one of the things like
[ __ ] conspiracies. Conspiracies are
busting out everywhere. One of the
newest ones that came up on my feed. Did
you guys know that Popeye
came about because the spinach big
spinach wanted to sell us more
vegetables?
God damn it. Yeah. [ __ ] it. I don't
know.
[ __ ] yeah. We got big speed bumps. We
got big spinach.
>> I love you guys.
[cheering]
Oh,
>> can't see me. Ladies and gentlemen,
>> what the [ __ ] is going on here, you
guys?
>> Let's hope the mic has gotten off the
rails tonight. Would you agree?
>> This has been such an off-road comedy
event.
>> Started off the rail. And by the way,
the only way you'd know how much this is
driving the our online audience crazy is
if you knew the chair. This chair has
been voted comedian of the night twice
by our online viewers. And now I'm
sitting on it AC Slater style. I'm just
rubbing it in their faces. Grundle first
>> in your favorite chair. All right, we
got one more comedian for the night. You
guys ready to call it out? You got one
more.
>> Bender, are you ready? Yeah, that's you,
buddy. They're clapping for you. Ladies
and gentlemen, your final comic of the
night. Uh it's his third time going up.
Uh he's been talking about his uh his
separation. So no, not tonight. Good. Uh
beer's got to stay off the stage though.
Stupid liquor wise. So you can you got
to point to it. Ladies and gentlemen,
here for our final act, Bender.
[cheering]
>> Thank you.
>> All right. You already stole like my
first two jokes. She made me leave my
prop on the table.
>> He told everyone it was my third time
up. I don't have any jokes left. So
yeah. Uh my name is Bender. Um I It's
really weird when you have a nickname
that doesn't describe you at all.
Does anyone else here have a nickname?
[laughter]
>> Trauma.
>> What trauma? What
>> drama?
The robot. The robot.
>> I have no idea what you're talking
about. Is there a robot named Bender?
What?
>> Never heard of it.
>> I just wanted to say thank you to those
two hecklers over there.
>> Um,
so I came here extreme
extremely prepared. I woke up 30 minutes
ago, rolled over here, didn't see any of
the other comedians, so I'm sure they
were all amazing.
Um,
so let's
>> This is this is my favorite set of spins
over here.
>> All right. Uh, let's just try to do some
crowd work cuz, you know, I'm an expert
comedian and I'm going to be great at
this.
>> Do something racist.
>> Do something racist. You know, I
>> I actually I have to say that's one of
the things I have the biggest problem
with about the comedians is that like
everyone's so mean. Like just just so
you know, like I'm I'm half black and
I'm I'm I'm half Jewish and I'm half
Christian
and I'm half lesbian and I'm half Karen
and I I take it on the fence.
>> Yeah, somebody got that.
>> Okay, who's just laughing over here?
>> You you What What do you do for a living
>> besides stand up?
Door Dash.
>> Door Dash.
>> Okay. What do you do for a living?
>> Say Say something funny.
>> Funny.
>> Something
funny.
Hold on. Sorry. I was waiting. I've been
waiting for this call.
>> No, no, not doing anything.
>> Yeah.
>> No, no, no. Just on stage.
>> All right. And we're going to call it
that.
>> Thank you.
[cheering]
>> That's the third time. Come back. The
fourth time is going to be even more
ridiculous.
Yeah, Bender, ladies and gentlemen.
>> Keep it going for Bender, ladies and
gentlemen. One more time for Vendor.
[applause]
>> [ __ ] I'm one. That's right. That's
what Bender is. All right, guys. Uh,
that's been the show. Did you have a
good time tonight?
>> What a weird show we got going on here,
huh?
>> If you had a good time, do me a favor.
Please tell your friends. And if you
didn't, do me a favor. Shut your [ __ ]
mouth. We don't
>> We don't need rumors. It's a small
island, you guys. No, you guys have been
a wonderful audience. This happens every
Monday night. I know like one one or two
people per table really had a good time.
So, come on back and bring another two
people and we'll see if they're weird
like you.
>> Saturday.
>> Oh, we got a show this Saturday. That's
right. That's right. Give me the
details. What are the deets?
>> It's by the sinkhole. It's Kihei.
>> It's by the sinkhole in Kihei behind
Fred. No longer the sinkhole in Kihei.
This Saturday night they'll be using the
power of equipment. So, uh, there will
be
>> loud sound there at 6:30 on Saturday,
right?
>> Sorry man on the sinkhole. Uh, guys,
this weekend is the Maui Food and Music
Festival over on the west side. Trisha
Dis going to be MCing. I'm going to be
hanging out by the pools all weekend. If
you're on the west side, come check it
out. Uh, other than that, see you guys
next Monday. Thanks for joining us. Give
it up for yourselves.
>> Give up for Oh, wait. I still got to
figure out audience member of the night,
don't I?
>> Audience member. audio.
>> No, he he wasn't here in the beginning.
>> You two were here since the beginning
and you two were here early, right? You
were here since the beginning, too,
right?
>> It's the chair.
>> So, we got two sets of audience members
of the night. I got two bottles of hot
sauce. One are going to each of you.
Thank you so much for joining us,
friends. You've been awesome audience
members. Don't forget to tell people
that you won something for being here.
So, if you didn't like the show, then
just be perseverant and you can win some
free hot sauce. All right, guys. You
know what I'm saying? Tip the bartender
staff. Good for Bay Coffee and Bar
putting on an awesome show for us. I'm
Chino. I hope you guys had a good time.
See you next week. Okay. Love you. Bye.
>> Bye.
>> End simulation.
It's where Los is playing this weekend.
>> Uh, right on the corner over here.
>> They said fix the chair. All right, calm
down.
>> [laughter]
>> Get more. You don't know what? Nobody
saw that. Nobody saw that.
[laughter]
>> The [ __ ]
>> Oh, thank you.
>> What's up, chat?
>> What's up, chat? Thanks for tuning in.
Hope you guys had a good time. Hey,
sorry you had to see the chair get
disrespected like that. Um, you see what
happens? You see what happens when you
have false idols.
Uh, no, there was no comic of the night
tonight. Uh, I was running too busy
tonight. Um,
>> oh, Frankie, you got the hot sauce. Hope
you enjoyed it. Please tell the chat how
good it is. Show crush tonight. Yeah,
something like that. It was an
interesting show tonight, that's for
sure. Can I send a bottle to the Cheers?
Oh, hold on. I'll be right back. I got
to give them their hot. Can you call her
pictures?
>> Hey, if y'all Venmo me 50 bucks, I'll
get Uncle Wy Ki to do an hour interview.
Got you, Uncle 50 bucks.
>> Put their clothes up.
like a beatboxing
beatboxing competition here.
>> That that happened like a month ago in
11 more months
handmade hot sauce uh some of the best
stuff on my island. Thank you for
joining us.
We do. We're making another batch.
>> We have 32 flavors already.
>> It's too much. People going flavor
blind. All right. Sorry about that. I
had to hand out the hot sauce for the
audience members uh of the of the night.
Appreciate it. Those other chairs picked
themselves up. Yeah, I know. It happened
really quickly. Hot sauce rock. Thank
you, Frankie. Oh, thank you, Bender. So
soft. So gentle. I couldn't tell if that
was your stubble or the stubble on my
head. Um, yeah, we we just scruffs.
That's the term for that.
>> Want to go hot sauce gang? Appreciate
you. Sausage. Um, if you guys Yes, I am
bald. This is correct. Uh, what's the
chair's OS? No, by the way, um, you got
to understand, I know that you said the
chair didn't give me consent, but uh,
it's my chair. Um, you know, it can't be
gross in your own chair. No, that's what
gross men say, "Uh, Jesus Christ, you
know, that was rough. You're always the
funniest." A thank you. I appreciate
that. Um, every Monday, this is every
Monday, 7:15, uh, Hawaii time. Um, that
elitist, uh, what's next week's topic?
Good question. I haven't decided yet.
Uh, I'm thinking about making it a super
interactive one. Um, perhaps, uh, heckle
night. It seems like it'll be heckle
night. Um, behind me, audience members
of the night.
Shino and the chair are engaged. That's
right. That's right. That's my chair.
It's my chair and I love her to death.
No. Uh funny thing. I got the chair from
uh from Sleep Number store. Um No, no,
no, no. I appreciate it. I appreciate
it. Uh I got it from the Sleep Number
store. Uh Sleep Number beds just
recently closed, so I got the chair for
free as well as a free bed.
Um, but funny funny thing is somebody
was sleeping outside the Sleep Number
store after it closed and like what's
your Sleep Number? Zero. Um, chairing
chairing is caring. Dude, you got I love
how much of an importance the chair has
become to you guys, bro. I I look like
Charles Barkley. Um, thank you. I'm
cross crossing racial borders. I
appreciate you saying that. My golf
swing is way better than his, though.
Um, I know that for sure. If you don't
know what I'm talking about, literally
type in YouTube Charles Barkley's Golf
Swing and enjoy the next 15 minutes.
It's hilarious. My hosting was topnotch.
Thank you, Rody. Appreciate you.
Gorgeous, Rody. You are gorgeous. You
beautiful, beautiful manu. Um, Ba is
okay.
>> I got to go.
>> I knew they would have voted for me if
they had the opportunity.
>> We didn't put up the vote tonight. We
didn't have the technology. Not going to
lie, Mondays are the best because of the
stream. A thanks life. Appreciate you.
We appreciate you tuning in. Life's a
script. I know. I've seen you in this
chat a bunch. You can laugh whenever you
want to, Doug. It's up to you. It truly
is. You can even laugh when things are
sad. That's uh it's your prerogative.
Totally. Need a taller chair. Need a
chair. A taller chair for Barkley. Um
you freed the chair from slavery.
[laughter]
Okay, relax.
Jesus. Uh definitely get crowd work. We
had crowd work last week. We might do
Headful Night like uh next week or maybe
we'll do um I don't know. Yeah, keep
keep winging some ideas. I'll I'll
figure it out before next week. Um,
laugh if you need help. [laughter]
Yeah, I can use some help. Uh, we still
voted comic is duo and Juno. Hey, you
know what? Me and the chair should take
us on the road. Uh, if we do do get to
do the show in the mainland, how about
this? Uh, the first show that we do in
the continental United States, I will
bring the chair. We will have the chair
in our first continental show. Um, I
just got to make sure I keep that chair
for that long. I I want to make sure
that this chair stays in your hearts as
long as possible.
Chair on tour. Uh Hector from Fast and
the Furious. I like that. Captain
Spalding is the one I get the most, but
I'll take I'll take that one. If you
ever redo your lo Oh, good idea. The
logo could be the chair. Was Who is
that? Is that Allison that said that?
Allison, you're brilliant. Appreciate
you, Miss Allison Wayland. One of our
favorite viewers. Allison. And who who's
that other gal that's always in here? I
appreciate Tessy.
Matt, Maddie, that's who it is. Maddie
and Allison, you're uh and Hollywood.
Y'all my favorite gals in this chat.
Appreciate y'all tuning in. You're
wonderful. Um chair merch coming soon.
Uh oh, you're a graphic designer,
Allison. That makes way too good a
sense. Uh need the high beams back. You
know, that's the thing about high beams
is they show up when Yeah. And Tessa and
you too, of course. Uh you've been
you've been loyal. We appreciate you,
Gal. Um super chat when we're trying to
get that soon. We're trying to monetize,
but for some reason, YouTube isn't
taking the next step. Uh, it's saying
apply now. Um, but the button's still
grayed out like we can't click it. So,
uh, write it to your local congressman
or write to your YouTube, um, organizer.
You know, it's good when what
the stream on YouTube. Yeah, you guys
have been solid to us, by the way. Thank
you so much, um, for giving our Monday's
purpose. This was always just a classic
normal Monday night comedy night. we
decided to live stream it and I'm so
glad we did. Um, you guys get to see
comedy in its rawest form and sure it's
bad. Sure, a lot of times it's bad, but
that's what the cutting edge and
innovation looks like. That's what it
feels like. You know, it feels
dangerous. It feels weird. Um, but some
of it is literally the most fresh level
of comedy that you're able to hear. So,
um, you get to rehearse [ __ ] all the
time on on Netflix and wherever you
want. This is your place to get comedy
in the wrong. Appreciate you guys. Uh,
I'm going to tune out. I'mma I'mma call
tonight, go to the gym in just a little
bit. Um, chair, chair, chair, one more
time for your viewing pleasure. The
chair, ladies and gentlemen.
>> Came. Jesus. Peach. Yeah. There you go,
friends. Your moment of zen.
>> Chair, chair, chair, chair, chair. Come
on, chat with me. Chat, chair, chair,
chair, chair, chair, chair, chair,
chair, chair. Now, you guys are awesome.
Appreciate you guys. Signing off. I'm
just going to end it right here. Have a
good night.
24 of them.